

PROFILE

I'm a web developer with more than 15 years of experience, i've worked in several web development projects as a team leader and developer with multidisciplinary teams, applying the latest technologies and embracing new challenges, since 2006.



EDUCATION

PLATZI / Course of Laravel

PLATZI / Course of API REST on Laravel

UNIR / Higher Technician / Advanced Technician in informatics



EXPERIENCE

TEAM LEADER/Deudu/2020-2022

Management of the development team and technology area, CRM development for callcenter, FrontEnd development Vuejs, Reactjs and Backend development in Laravel 7 and Mysql, development of some integrations with Twillo API to send whatsapp message and make calls.

Backend Developer/Nivelics/2020-2020

I was the responsibilities to make a REST API Development in Laravel and Symphony.

FullStack Developer/Lupatech/2019-2020

I was made a eLearning System with stack MEAN and I use the materialize framework to manage all components.

Junior Developer/Hospital el Rosario/2006-2016

I made a different apps on php and mysql in the last 2 years working in this company I was made all the apps under cakephp 2 framework and bootstrap framework.



SKILLS

Javascript (10 years)
JQuery (10 years)
Php (15 years)
HTML (15 years)
Node JS (1 year)
CSS (15 years)
Laravel (3 years)
Vuejs (3 years)
MySQL (15 years)

